University of Connecticut 1998.0186
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, 1962-1972
  - 1963-1964
    - New England Association of Colleges & Secondary Schools (Box 26:, Folder 387)
    - New England Council (Box 26:, Folder 388)
    - New England Board of Higher Education (Box 27:, Folder 389-390)
    - Norris, Robert (Dean, Continuing Education Service) (Box 27:, Folder 391)
    - Norwich, - New London Branch or Middlesex County Branch (Box 27:, Folder 392)
    - Northby, Arwood S. (Dean of Students) (Box 27:, Folder 393)
    - O (Box 27:, Folder 394)
    - OE CD (Box 27:, Folder 395)
    - P - P1 (Box 27:, Folder 396)
    - Pomfret School (Box 27:, Folder 397)
    - Powers, John, E. (Placement office) (Box 27:, Folder 398)
    - President's Council (Box 27:, Folder 399)
    - President's Newsletter (Box 27:, Folder 400)
    - Public Works Department (Box 27:, Folder 401)
    - Re (Box 27:, Folder 402)
    - Religious Education (Box 28:, Folder 403)
    - Research Corporation (Box 28:, Folder 404)
    - Research Grants (Box 28:, Folder 405-410)
    - Research Grants (Box 29:, Folder 411-412)
    - Research Foundation (Box 29:, Folder 413-414)
    - Rhodes scholarships (Box 29:, Folder 415)
    - Rhodesia Project (Box 29:, Folder 416)
    - Ro (Box 29:, Folder 417)
    - Roberts, Thomas E. (Director of Admissions) (Box 29:, Folder 418)
    - Sanders, William J. (Box 29:, Folder 419)
    - Sch (Box 29:, Folder 420)
    - Schneller, Richard F. (Member, Board of Trustees) (Box 29:, Folder 421)
    - Scholarships and Gifts (Box 29:, Folder 422-423)
    - Scholarships and Gifts (Box 30:, Folder 424-425)
    - Science Talent awards (Box 30:, Folder 426)
    - Se (Box 30:, Folder 427)
    - Selective Service (Box 30:, Folder 428)
    - Si (Box 30:, Folder 429)
    - Sistare, Willard (Manger, Jorgensen Auditorium) (Box 30:, Folder 430)
    - St (Box 30:, Folder 431)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 30:, Folder 432)
    - State Comptoller (Box 30:, Folder 433)
    - State Health Department (Box 30:, Folder 434)
    - State Highway Department (Box 30:, Folder 435)
    - State Police Department (Box 30:, Folder 436)
    - Sterling, M. Elizabeth (Member, Board of Trustees) (Box 30:, Folder 437)
    - Wallace Stevens memorial lectures (Box 30:, Folder 438)
    - Stowe, Lyman (Dean, Medical School) (Box 30:, Folder 439)
    - Students to be contacted (Box 30:, Folder 440)
    - Student Senate (Box 30:, Folder 441-443)
    - Student Union Board and Building (Box 31:, Folder 444)
    - “Students Rights” (Box 31:, Folder 445)
    - Su (Box 31:, Folder 446)
    - Taft School (Box 31:, Folder 447)
    - Tappan, Frances (Box 31:, Folder 448)
    - To (Box 31:, Folder 449)
    - Torrington Branch (Box 31:, Folder 450)
    - Trecker, Harleigh B. (Dean, School of Social Work) (Box 31:, Folder 451)
    - U (Box 31:, Folder 452)
    - University Bank (Box 31:, Folder 453)
    - Underwater Center (Box 31:, Folder 454)
    - University Foundation (Box 31:, Folder 455)
    - University of Connecticut Foundation (Box 31:, Folder 456)
    - University Senate (Box 31:, Folder 457)
    - University Senate Material (Box 32:, Folder 458-464)
    - University Secondary School [ E.O. Smith High School] (Box 33:, Folder 465)
    - University Professors (Box 33:, Folder 466)
    - University Scholars (Box 33:, Folder 467)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 33:, Folder 468)
    - U.S. Health, Education and Welfare (Box 33:, Folder 469-470)
    - Van Bibber, E. George (Box 33:, Folder 471)
    - Voice of America (Box 33:, Folder 472)
    - W (Box 33:, Folder 473)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 33:, Folder 474)
    - Watson, Elmer S. (Member, Board of Trustees) (Box 33:, Folder 475)
    - Waugh, Albert E. (Box 33:, Folder 476)
    - Waugh, Albert E. (Box 34:, Folder 477)
    - We (Box 34:, Folder 478)
    - Westminster School (Box 34:, Folder 479)
    - Westover School (Box 34:, Folder 480)
    - Wh (Box 34:, Folder 481)
    - Whetten, Nathan L. (Box 34:, Folder 482)
    - WHUS (Box 34:, Folder 483)
    - Wi (Box 34:, Folder 484)
    - Widmer, Carolyn (Dean, School of Nursing) (Box 34:, Folder 485)
    - Windham Community Memorial Hospital (Box 34:, Folder 486)
    - Wo (Box 34:, Folder 487)
    - X, Y (Box 34:, Folder 488)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 34:, Folder 489)
    - Young, W. B. (Dean, College of Agriculture) (Box 34:, Folder 490)
  - 1964-1965
    - A (Box 35:, Folder 491)
    - Administrative Reports (Box 35:, Folder 492)
    - Advisers (Box 35:, Folder 493)
    - African Scholarship Program (ASPAU) (Box 35:, Folder 494)
    - African - American Institute, (2 folders) (Box 35:, Folder 495)
    - Air Force (Box 35:, Folder 496)
    - Alumni (Box 35:, Folder 497)
    - An (Box 35:, Folder 498)
    - Arboretum (Box 35:, Folder 499)
    - Architects (Box 35:, Folder 500)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 35:, Folder 501)
    - Attorney General (Box 35:, Folder 502)
    - Austin, J. H. (Comptroller) (Box 35:, Folder 503)
    - B (Box 36:, Folder 504)
    - Babbidge - personal (Box 36:, Folder 505-510)
    - Babbidge - correspondence (Box 37:, Folder 511-516)
    - Babbidge - correspondence (Box 38:, Folder 517)
    - Babbidge, Homer D. (Box 38:, Folder 518-519)
    - Bailey, Barbara (Trustee) (Box 38:, Folder 520)
    - Be (Box 38:, Folder 521)
    - Benton, William (Trustee) (Box 38:, Folder 522)
    - Bequests (Box 38:, Folder 523)
    - Bi (Box 38:, Folder 524)
    - Bishop, Merlin D. (Trustee) (Box 38:, Folder 525)
    - Bo (Box 38:, Folder 526)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 38:, Folder 527)
    - Borge, Victor (Box 38:, Folder 528)
    - Br (Box 38:, Folder 529)
    - Brotman, Michael M. (Manager, Auditorium) (Box 39:, Folder 530)
    - Budds, John J. (Trustee) (Box 39:, Folder 531)
    - Budget, University (Box 39:, Folder 532)
    - Budget, State Division of (Box 39:, Folder 533)
    - C (Box 39:, Folder 534)
    - Campus, Daily (student newspaper) (Box 39:, Folder 535)
    - Canadian Conference (Mrs. Mary Hall James) (Box 39:, Folder 536)
    - Capital Projects (Box 39:, Folder 537)
    - Carter, W. H. (Dean, Arts & Sciences) (Box 39:, Folder 538)
    - Christian, J. O. (Box 39:, Folder 539)
    - Ce (Box 39:, Folder 540)
    - Clark, Hugh (Box 39:, Folder 541)
    - Civil Defense (Box 39:, Folder 542)
    - Civil Rights (Box 39:, Folder 543)
    - Co (Box 39:, Folder 544)
    - Cohen, Summer (Box 39:, Folder 545)
    - College Entrance Examination Board (Box 40:, Folder 546-549)
    - College of the Virgin Islands (Box 40:, Folder 550)
    - Commencement (Box 40:, Folder 551)
    - Commendations and Complaint (Box 41:, Folder 552)
    - Committee
      - Reports (Box 41:, Folder 553-554)
      - Trustee, Administration, Faculty (Box 41:, Folder 555)
      - Carter Replacement (Box 41:, Folder 556)
      - Advisory on Comp. Mental Health Planning (Box 41:, Folder 557-558)
      - Commission on Higher Education (Box 42:, Folder 559)
      - Arjona Replacement (Box 42:, Folder 560)
      - Exhibits (Box 42:, Folder 561)
      - Letters (Box 42:, Folder 562)
      - Lakes and ponds ( A.J.R. Guttary, chairman) (Box 42:, Folder 563)
      - Liaison - Board of Trustees - State Board of Education (Box 42:, Folder 564)
      - Naming of Buildings (Box 42:, Folder 565)
      - Space and planning ( David Philips, chairman) (Box 42:, Folder 566)
      - Solicitation and vending ( Charles Owen, chairman) (Box 42:, Folder 567)
      - Spiritual life of students (Box 42:, Folder 568)
      - State Education TV (Box 42:, Folder 569)
      - State on Library Improvement (Box 42:, Folder 570)
    - Computer Center (Box 42:, Folder 571)
    - Condolences (Box 42:, Folder 572)
    - Conferences (Box 42:, Folder 573)
    - Connecticut Council on Higher Education (Box 42:, Folder 574)
    - Connecticut Council for Pre-college Science Education (Box 42:, Folder 575)
    - Connecticut Development Commissions (Box 43:, Folder 576)
    - Connecticut Education Association (Box 43:, Folder 577)
    - Connecticut Education T.V. Corporation (Box 43:, Folder 578)
    - Connecticut Foundation for Independent Schools (Box 43:, Folder 579)
    - Coo (Box 43:, Folder 580)
    - D (Box 43:, Folder 581)
    - Dean's Council (Box 43:, Folder 582)
    - Deans and directors (Box 43:, Folder 583)
    - Department Council - Anti-poverty Bill (Box 43:, Folder 584)
    - Do (Box 43:, Folder 585)
    - Donahue, A. J. (Box 43:, Folder 586)
    - Dormitories (Box 43:, Folder 587)
    - Dr (Box 43:, Folder 588)
    - Driscoll, Paul J. (Trustee) (Box 43:, Folder 589)
    - Dunlop, John (Box 43:, Folder 590)
    - E (Box 43:, Folder 591)
    - Eastern States Exposition (Box 43:, Folder 592)
    - Education, School of (Box 43:, Folder 593)
    - Education, State Department of (Box 43:, Folder 594)
    - En (Box 43:, Folder 595)
    - Engineering, School of (Box 43:, Folder 596)
    - Engineering Research Center (Box 43:, Folder 597)
    - Enrollments (Box 43:, Folder 598)
    - Evans, John M. (Box 43:, Folder 599)
    - F (Box 44:, Folder 600)
    - Faculty - Alumni Center (Box 44:, Folder 601)
    - Faculty - Publications (Box 44:, Folder 602)
    - Faculty - Scholarships (Box 44:, Folder 603)
    - Fingles, Franklin O. (Box 44:, Folder 604)
    - Financial Aid (Box 44:, Folder 605)
    - Finance and Control - State Department of (Box 44:, Folder 606)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 44:, Folder 607)
    - Fo (Box 44:, Folder 608)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 44:, Folder 609)
    - Foreign Policy Association (Box 44:, Folder 610)
    - Foreign students (Box 44:, Folder 611)
    - Fraternities and Sororities (Box 44:, Folder 612)
    - Fox, Lewis (Dean, School of Dental Medicine) (Box 45:, Folder 613)
    - Friedman, Don (Director, Publicity and Public Relations) (Box 45:, Folder 614)
    - Fuller, Alfred C. (Trustee) (Box 45:, Folder 615)
    - Gant, Edward V. (Provost - Elect) (Box 45:, Folder 616)
    - Ge (Box 45:, Folder 617)
    - Gi (Box 45:, Folder 618)
    - Gill, Joseph N. (Trustee) (Box 45:, Folder 619)
    - Golf Course (Box 45:, Folder 620)
    - Governor of Connecticut (Box 45:, Folder 621)
    - Gr (Box 45:, Folder 622)
    - H (Box 45:, Folder 623)
    - Hartford Hospital (Box 45:, Folder 624)
    - Hartford Branch (Box 45:, Folder 625)
    - Harvey, Robert O. (Dean, School of Business Administration) (Box 45:, Folder 626)
    - Har (Box 45:, Folder 627)
    - Health Service (Box 45:, Folder 628)
    - Hewitt, Harold G. (Dean, School of Pharmacy) (Box 45:, Folder 629)
    - Ho (Box 45:, Folder 630)
    - Honors program (Box 45:, Folder 631)
    - Hopkins, Bert (Dean, School of Law) (Box 45:, Folder 632)
    - Hu (Box 45:, Folder 633)
    - I (Box 45:, Folder 634)
    - Institute of
      - Cellular Biology (Box 45:, Folder 635)
      - Gerontology (Box 45:, Folder 636)
      - Human Development ( David Phillips, chairman) (Box 45:, Folder 637)
      - International Education (Box 45:, Folder 638)
      - Marine Research (Box 45:, Folder 639)
      - Nutrition and Food Science (Box 45:, Folder 640)
      - Urban Research (Box 45:, Folder 641)
      - Water Resources (Box 46:, Folder 642)
    - International Studies, Center of (Box 46:, Folder 643)
    - Institute of Public Service (Box 46:, Folder 644)
    - J (Box 46:, Folder 645)
    - Joint projects office (Box 46:, Folder 646)
    - K (Box 46:, Folder 647)
    - Kellogg Foundation (Box 46:, Folder 648)
    - Ki (Box 46:, Folder 649)
    - Labor Education Center (Box 46:, Folder 650)
    - Land-Grant College Association (Box 46:, Folder 651-652)
    - Land Purchases (Box 46:, Folder 653)
    - Legal Counsel questionnaire (Box 46:, Folder 656)
    - Legislation - State (Box 46:, Folder 657)
    - Legislation - Federal (Box 46:, Folder 658)
    - Library (Box 46:, Folder 659)
    - Loeb Awards (Box 46:, Folder 660)
    - Long-range planning - University Committee on (Box 46:, Folder 661)
    - M (Box 47:, Folder 662)
    - Mahoney, Mary Hannan - Dedication (Box 47:, Folder 663)
    - Manning, Stuart (Box 47:, Folder 664)
    - Map (Box 47:, Folder 665)
    - Material Science Center (Box 47:, Folder 666)
    - Maxcy, Ellis C. (Trustee) (Box 47:, Folder 667)
    - McCullouch, Donald (Coordinator, Student Activities) (Box 47:, Folder 668)
    - McMahon, Brien (Hall) - Dedication (Box 47:, Folder 669)
    - McMahon, Brien - Lecture Series (Box 47:, Folder 670)
    - Me (Box 47:, Folder 671)
    - Medical - Dental School (Box 47:, Folder 672-673)
    - Mental Health Talk Material - Babbidge (Box 47:, Folder 674)
    - Mi (Box 47:, Folder 675)
    - Military day (Box 47:, Folder 676)
    - Military department (Box 47:, Folder 677)
    - Mo (Box 47:, Folder 678)
    - Moreland, Wallace (Box 47:, Folder 679)
    - N (Box 47:, Folder 680)
    - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators (Box 47:, Folder 681)
    - National Catholic Education Association (Box 47:, Folder 682)
    - National Commission on Accrediting (Box 47:, Folder 683)
    - National Scholarship Service and Fund of Negro Students (Box 47:, Folder 684)
    - National Education Association (Box 47:, Folder 685)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 47:, Folder 686)
    - Nelson, Don (Box 48:, Folder 687)
    - Newcomen Society, Member 10/21/64 (Box 48:, Folder 688)
    - New England Land-Grant College Presidents (Box 48:, Folder 689)
    - New England Council (Box 48:, Folder 690)
    - New England Presidents meeting - Babbidge (Box 48:, Folder 691)
    - New Positions (Box 48:, Folder 692)
    - Nolan, Francena (Dean, Home Economics) (Box 48:, Folder 693)
    - Norris, Robert B. (Dean, Continuing Education Services) (Box 48:, Folder 694)
    - Northby, Arwood, S. (Dean of Students) (Box 48:, Folder 695)
    - Norwich-New London and Middlesex County Branches (Box 48:, Folder 696)
    - O'Brien, Bishop - Gift (Box 48:, Folder 697)
    - P (Box 48:, Folder 698)
    - Pomfret School (Box 48:, Folder 699)
    - Powers, John (Placement office) (Box 48:, Folder 700)
    - President's Council (Box 48:, Folder 701)
    - PSAC (Box 48:, Folder 702)
    - Public Works Department (Box 48:, Folder 703)
    - Q (Box 48:, Folder 704)
    - Recommendations (Box 48:, Folder 705)
    - Religious Education (Box 48:, Folder 706)
    - Real Estate (Box 48:, Folder 707)
    - Research Corporation (Box 49:, Folder 708)
    - Research Foundation (Box 49:, Folder 709)
    - Research grants (Box 49:, Folder 710-712)
    - Rhodes scholarship (Box 49:, Folder 713)
    - Ro (Box 49:, Folder 714)
    - S (Box 49:, Folder 715)
    - Sailing Club (Box 49:, Folder 716)
    - Sch (Box 49:, Folder 717)
    - Scholarships and Gifts (Box 49:, Folder 718-719)
    - Scholarships and Gifts (Box 50:, Folder 720-721)
    - Science Talent Awards (Box 50:, Folder 722)
    - Security Insurance Group (Box 50:, Folder 723)
    - Sh (Box 50:, Folder 724)
    - Si (Box 50:, Folder 725)
    - Sistare, Willard (Manager, Jorgensen Auditorium) (Box 50:, Folder 726)
    - Skating Rink (Box 50:, Folder 727)
    - Speech material (Box 50:, Folder 728)
    - St (Box 50:, Folder 729)
    - Stamford Branch (Box 50:, Folder 730)
    - State
      - Comptroller (Box 50:, Folder 731)
      - Development (Box 50:, Folder 732)
      - of Connecticut (Box 50:, Folder 733)
      - Highway Department (Box 50:, Folder 734)
      - Personnel Department (Box 50:, Folder 736)
      - Police Department (Box 50:, Folder 737)
    - Sterling, M. Elizabeth (Box 50:, Folder 738)
    - Stevens, Wallace - Memorial lectures (Box 50:, Folder 739)
    - Stowe, Lyman (Dean, Medical Schools) (Box 50:, Folder 740)
    - Students Insurance (Box 50:, Folder 741)
    - Student Union Board and Building (Box 50:, Folder 742)
    - Students, Letters to (Box 50:, Folder 743-744)
    - Students, Letters to (Box 51:, Folder 745-747)
    - Student Senate (Box 51:, Folder 748)
    - Summer Theatre (Box 51:, Folder 749)
    - Summer Youth Orchestra (Box 51:, Folder 750)
    - Taft School (Box 51:, Folder 751)
    - Title VIII, Housing Act of 1964 (Box 51:, Folder 752)
    - To (Box 51:, Folder 753)
    - U (Box 51:, Folder 754)
    - Torrington Branch (Box 51:, Folder 755)
    - Trees (Box 51:, Folder 756)
    - Trecker, Harleigh B. (Box 52:, Folder 757)
    - Underwater Center (Box 52:, Folder 758)
    - University Band (Box 52:, Folder 759)
    - University Foundation (Box 52:, Folder 760)
    - University Museum (Box 52:, Folder 761)
    - University Scholars (Box 52:, Folder 762)
    - University Press (Box 52:, Folder 763)
    - University Professor (Box 52:, Folder 764)
    - University Secondary School (Box 52:, Folder 765)
    - University Security Police (Box 52:, Folder 766)
    - University Senate (Box 52:, Folder 767-768)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 52:, Folder 769)
    - U.S. Health, Education and Welfare (Box 52:, Folder 770-771)
    - V (Box 52:, Folder 772)
    - Van Bibber, E. George (Physical Education) (Box 52:, Folder 773)
    - Veterinary Medicine, School of (Box 52:, Folder 774)
    - W (Box 52:, Folder 775)
    - Waterbury Branch (Box 52:, Folder 776)
    - Waterford Branch (Box 52:, Folder 777)
    - Watson, Elmer S. (Trustee) (Box 52:, Folder 778)
    - Waugh, Albert E. (Box 53:, Folder 779-780)
    - Westover School (Box 53:, Folder 781)
    - Wh (Box 53:, Folder 782)
    - Whetten, Nathan (Box 53:, Folder 783)
    - Wi (Box 53:, Folder 784)
    - Widmer, Carolyn (Dean, School of Nursing) (Box 53:, Folder 785)
    - Windham Community Memorial Hospital (Box 53:, Folder 786)
    - Wo (Box 53:, Folder 787)
    - Women Leaders (Box 53:, Folder 788)
    - World Youth Forum (Box 53:, Folder 789)
    - X, Y (Box 53:, Folder 790)
    - Yankee Conference (Box 53:, Folder 791)
    - Young, W. B. (Dean, College of Agriculture) (Box 53:, Folder 792)
  - 1965-1966
    - Administrative Reports (Box 54:, Folder 793)
    - African-American Institute (Box 54:, Folder 794)
    - African Scholarship Program (ASPAU) (Box 54:, Folder 795)
    - Agency for International Development (AID) (Box 54:, Folder 796)
    - Alumni (Box 54:, Folder 797)
    - Alumni Questionnaire - UCLA (Box 54:, Folder 798)
    - Arboretum (Box 54:, Folder 799)
    - Architects (Box 54:, Folder 800)
    - Association of Governing Boards of State Universities and Allied Institutions (Box 54:, Folder 801)
    - Attorney General (Box 54:, Folder 802)
    - Atomic Energy Commission (Box 54:, Folder 803)
    - Bailey, Barbara (Trustee) (Box 54:, Folder 804)
    - Benton, William (Trustee) (Box 54:, Folder 805)
    - Bishop, Merlin D. (Trustee) (Box 54:, Folder 806)
    - Board of Trustees (Box 54:, Folder 807)
    - Borge, Victor (Box 54:, Folder 808)
    - Braitmayer Foundation (Box 54:, Folder 809)
    - Brotman, Michael M. (Manager, Auditorium) (Box 54:, Folder 810)
    - Budds, John J. (Trustee) (Box 54:, Folder 811)
    - Budget, University (Box 54:, Folder 812)
    - Business Administration, School of (Box 54:, Folder 813)
    - C (Box 54:, Folder 814)
    - Campus, Daily (student newspaper) (Box 54:, Folder 815)
    - Carter, W. Harrison (Dean, Arts and Science) (Box 54:, Folder 816)
    - Canadian Conference (May Hall James) (Box 55:, Folder 817)
    - Capital Projects (Box 55:, Folder 818)
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York (Box 55:, Folder 819)
    - Carillon (Box 55:, Folder 820)
    - Christian, J. O. (Box 55:, Folder 821)
    - Civil Defense (Box 55:, Folder 822)
    - Civil Right (Box 55:, Folder 823)
    - Clark, Hugh (Box 55:, Folder 824)
    - Co (Box 55:, Folder 825)
    - Coast Guard Academy (Box 55:, Folder 826)
    - Cohen, Sumner (Box 55:, Folder 827)
    - College Entrance Exam Board (Box 55:, Folder 828)
    - College of the Virgin Islands (Box 55:, Folder 829)
    - Commencement (Box 55:, Folder 830)
    - Commission on Higher Education (Box 55:, Folder 831)
    - Committee
      - Spiritual Life of Students (Box 55:, Folder 832)
      - Carter Replacement (Box 55:, Folder 833)
      - Christian Replacement (Box 55:, Folder 834)
      - Hopkins Replacement (Box 55:, Folder 835)
      - Replace Dean Nolan (Box 55:, Folder 836)
      - Young Replacement (Box 55:, Folder 837)
      - Advisory, for work in Gerontology (Box 55:, Folder 838)
      - Retirement Policies (Box 55:, Folder 839)
      - Exhibits (Box 55:, Folder 840)
      - Lakes and Ponds ( A. J. R. Guttay, chairman) (Box 55:, Folder 841)
      - Advisory, Athletic (Box 55:, Folder 842-843)
      - University Design Review (Box 55:, Folder 844)
      - Advisory for the Biomedical Sciences Support (Box 55:, Folder 845)
      - Advisory, Auditorium and Little Theatre (Box 55:, Folder 846)
      - Extension Study (Box 55:, Folder 847)
      - Naming of Buildings (Box 56:, Folder 848)
      - University Long-Range Planning (Box 56:, Folder 849)
    - Connecticut - Long Island Bridge (Box 56:, Folder 850)
    - Connecticut Educational T.V. Corporation (Box 56:, Folder 851)
    - Connecticut Council on Crime and Delinquency (Box 56:, Folder 852)
    - Connecticut Research Commission (Box 56:, Folder 853)
    - Council, Departmental - Anti-Poverty Bill (Box 56:, Folder 854)
    - Contracts (Box 56:, Folder 855)
    - Council, University on Water Resource (Box 56:, Folder 856)
    - COSERV - Mrs. Woodhouse, June 1966 (Box 56:, Folder 857)
    - Danforth Foundation (Box 56:, Folder 858)
    - Dean's Council (Box 56:, Folder 859)
    - Dormitories (Box 56:, Folder 860)
    - E (Box 56:, Folder 861)
    - Education, School of (Box 56:, Folder 862)
    - Engineering Research Center (Box 56:, Folder 863)
    - Enrollments (Box 56:, Folder 864)
    - Evans, John M. (Box 56:, Folder 865)
    - Faculty - Alumni Center (Box 56:, Folder 866)
    - Farner, Frank (Box 56:, Folder 867)
    - Finance and Control, State Department of (Box 56:, Folder 868)
    - Fine Arts, School of (Box 56:, Folder 869)
    - Fingles, Franklin O. (Box 56:, Folder 870)
    - Ford Foundation (Box 56:, Folder 871)
    - Foreign Students (Box 56:, Folder 872)
    - Fraternities and Sororities (Box 56:, Folder 873)
    - G (Box 57:, Folder 874)
    - Golf Course (Box 57:, Folder 875)
    - Governor of Connecticut (Box 57:, Folder 876)
    - Gant, Edward V. (Acting Provost) (Box 57:, Folder 877)
    - Glider Ride (Box 57:, Folder 878)
    - H (Box 57:, Folder 879)
    - Health Center (Dr. Lewis and Dr. John Patterson) (Box 57:, Folder 880-883)
    - Health Service (Dr. J. LeRoy) (Box 57:, Folder 884)
    - Hewes, Robert E. (Dean of Students) (Box 57:, Folder 885)
    - Hewitt, Harold G. (Dean, School of Pharmacy) (Box 57:, Folder 886)
    - Internship Program (Box 57:, Folder 887)
    - Institute of
      - Cellular Biology (Box 57:, Folder 888)
      - International Studies (Box 57:, Folder 889)
      - Living (Box 57:, Folder 890)
      - Marine Research ( John S. Rankin, Director) (Box 57:, Folder 891)
      - Public Service (Box 57:, Folder 892)
      - Urban Research (Box 57:, Folder 893)
      - Water Resources (Box 57:, Folder 894)
    - Jewish Theological Seminary (Box 57:, Folder 895)
    - K (Box 57:, Folder 896)
    - Kansas City Conference (Box 57:, Folder 897)
    - Kellogg Foundation (Box 57:, Folder 898)
    - Labor Education Center (Box 58:, Folder 899)
    - Loeb file to WSM (Box 58:, Folder 900)
    - Land-Grant College Association (Box 58:, Folder 901-902)
    - Legislation - Federal (Box 58:, Folder 903)
    - Legislation - State (Box 58:, Folder 904)
    - Library (Box 58:, Folder 905)
    - M (Box 58:, Folder 906)
    - Material Science Center (Box 58:, Folder 907)
    - McMahon, Brien - Lecture Series (Box 58:, Folder 908)
    - Mystic Seaport (Box 58:, Folder 909)
    - National Science Foundation (Box 58:, Folder 910)
    - New England Land-Grant College Presidents (Box 58:, Folder 911)
    - Noah Webster Foundation (Box 58:, Folder 912)
    - Powers, John (Placement office) (Box 58:, Folder 913)